Guide to the John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
Taber, John papers
- Chronological Files, 1938-1960
  - Partial List of ECA Employees and Their Subversive Affiliations, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Passports, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Passports, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Patronage, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Personnel, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - Personnel Loaned to House Appropriations Committee, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Photos of JT, Aides and Two Women on a Junket to Greece, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - Prerequisites for Government Subsidies for Conservation Practices, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Publications, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Put Yourself in Marshall's Place, by James P. Warburg, private publication, Date Unknown (Box 141)
  - Q, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - Qualifications and Experience of U.S. Personnel Participating in the Preparation of the European Recovery Program, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - R, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - R.F.C., Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Radio - WCHN, Norwich, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Railroad Retirement, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Receipts - Stationery, Room and Stamps, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Reduction of Non-Essential Federal Expenditure, Date Unknown (Box 154)
  - Referrals, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Referrals, Date Unknown (Box 147)
  - Report of Committee on Reduction of Federal Spending and re Civilian Employment, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - Report On The Greek Situation and Economic Cooperation Administration (outgrowth of Marshall Plan), Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Report on Use of Governmental Researchers and Business Analysis, on a Loan Basis, by the House Appropriations Committee, 80th Congress, 2nd Session, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Republican Delegation, N.Y.S., Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - Republican Members, 80th Congress, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Republican Members, 81st Congress, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Republican Members, 83rd Congress, Date Unknown (Box 139)
  - Robert E. Lee, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Robert J. Anderson, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Rossee, Bernhard, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Ruby Parsons, Date Unknown (Box 167)
  - S, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - S. W. (Wat) Arnold, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Sampson Air Force Base, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - School Lunch Program, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - Schuyler County, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Schuyler County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Selective Service, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Selective Service, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Senate Bills, 83rd Congress, Second Session, Date Unknown (Box 136)
  - Seneca County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Seneca Ordinance Depot, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Seneca Ordnance, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Seneca Ordnance Depot, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Small bundle of miscellaneous papers, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Small Business, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Small Business Administration, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Small Business Administration, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Social Security, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Social Security, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Social Security, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - State Department, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - State Department, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - State Department, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - State, Commerce and Justice, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Statement by Sec. Royal re Request for Supplemental Appropriation for Government and Relief in Occupied Areas, Date Unknown (Box 129)
  - Statements, John Taber, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Statements, Other Members, Date Unknown (Box 154)
  - Stevens, Fred, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Sugar, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - Survey Report on Federal Security Agency - Field Organization and Management, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - T - Y, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Tariff, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Taylor, Sutherland G., Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Text of Taber Amendment to H. J. Res. 277, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - Theodore Roosevelt, Reference File, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Tompkins County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Tompkins County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Treasury, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Treasury - Post Office, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Treasury and Post Office, Date Unknown (Box 115)
  - Treasury Department, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Treasury Department, Date Unknown (Box 124)
  - Turkish Newspapers, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - Two Illegible Senate Memos, Date Unknown (Box 130)
  - U.S.I.A., Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Agency, Date Unknown (Box 142)
  - United States Government - Foreign Translation, Date Unknown (Box 116)
  - V, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - VA Hospital, Syracuse, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Veterans General, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Veterans General, Date Unknown (Box 97)
  - Voice of America, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Voice of America, Date Unknown (Box 137)
  - Voting Record, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Vouchers for Office Expenses, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - W, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - W. Kings land Macy, Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - War, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - War Agencies, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - War Department, Discharges, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - War Department, General, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - War Department, Personnel, Date Unknown (Box 123)
  - War Relocation Authority, Date Unknown (Box 126)
  - Washington, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Weekly Digest, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - White House, Date Unknown (Box 154)
  - Williams, George E., Date Unknown (Box 166)
  - Yates County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 103)
  - Yates County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 148)
  - Z, Date Unknown (Box 123)
- Alphabetical Files, 1933-1953
  - Ontario National Bank of Clifton Springs, 1933-1941 (Box 149)
  - Beacon Milling Company, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Charles A. Noble, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Charles M. Watkins, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Charles S. Hewitt, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Greenberg, Harry S., 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Georgian Peck, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - James H. Chase, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Jenkins Laboratory, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Maurice D. Richards, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Victor Insulation Incorporation, 1935-1941 (Box 54)
  - Agriculture - Beans, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Agriculture A.D.J. Administration, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Agriculture Credit Matters, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Agriculture Department, Food and Drug Administration, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - American Legion, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Anon, Letters, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Archives, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - At water, Florence B., 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Auburn Office, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Auburn Office, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Auburn Office Correspondence, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Auburn Shoes Incorporated, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Auburn Trust Company, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Aviation, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Banks, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Bituminous Coal Company, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Boy Scouts, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Brains Trust, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Breweries, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Campaign, 1937 (Box 62)
  - City of Auburn, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1937-1945 (Box 61)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Rationing, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Reapportionment of N.Y.S., 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - State Department, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Stationery Receipts, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Veterans Administration, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - W.P.A, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - W.P.B., 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Wage and Hour Division, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - War Production Board, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Washington Office, 1937-1945 (Box 62)
  - Workers Alliance, 1937-1939 (Box 49)
  - Convention State, 1938 (Box 47)
  - Theatre Projects, 1938-1939 (Box 49)
  - Workers Alliance and Communism, 1938-1941 (Box 49)
  - Congressional Directory, 1938-05-1947-01 (Box 149)
  - Football tickets, 1939 (Box 47)
  - Investigative Committee, WPA, 1939 (Box 49)
  - Invitations, 1939 (Box 48)
  - Theatre Project, WPA, Writers' Projects, Federal Arts Projects, 1939 (Box 49)
  - WPA Main Office, 1939 (Box 49)
  - Writers and Arts Projects, 1939 (Box 49)
  - Campaign, 1940 (Box 62)
  - Census, 1940 (Box 47)
  - Convention, 1940 (Box 47)
  - Football tickets, 1940-1941 (Box 47)
  - Labor Department, 1940-01 (Box 49)
  - Congressional Record, 1940-01-01 (Box 47)
  - Inauguration, 1941 (Box 48)
  - Capitol, 1941-01-1946-12 (Box 149)
  - District of Columbia, 1942-1946 (Box 149)
  - Navy Department, 1942 (Box 49)
  - Annapolis 1943 Report, 1943 (Box 61)
  - Campaign, 1944 (Box 62)
  - Navy Department Commissions and Enlisted Ratings, 1944 (Box 49)
  - Navy, General, 1944 (Box 49)
  - Veterans, 1944-1946 (Box 150)
  - Veterans, Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 150)
  - War Production Board, 1944 (Box 150)
  - War Shipping Administration, Merchant Marines, 1944 (Box 150)
  - War Shipping Board, 1944 (Box 150)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1945-1946 (Box 149)
  - Immigration - Reentry, 1945 (Box 149)
  - Introductory Letters, 1945-1946 (Box 149)
  - Republican County Committees - 38th District, Campaign File, 1945 (Box 149)
  - Republican Party, National, 1945 (Box 150)
  - War Food, 1945 (Box 150)
  - Invitations, 1945-01-01 (Box 48)
  - Auburn Office, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Civilian Production Administration, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Claims, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Commodity Credit, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Immigration, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Invitations, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Liquor, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Maritime Commission, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Naval Training Center, Sampson, 1946 (Box 149)
  - New York State Matters, 1946 (Box 149)
  - O.P.A. General, 1946 (Box 150)
  - Ovid Telephone Company, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Public Buildings, 1946 (Box 150)
  - Selective Service, 1946 (Box 150)
  - Snap Beans, 1946 (Box 149)
  - Surplus Property, 1946 (Box 150)
  - UNRRA, 1946 (Box 150)
  - War Department, General, 1946 (Box 150)
  - War Department, Personnel, 1946 (Box 150)
  - Civil Service and Employment, 1946-04-01-1947-01-01 (Box 149)
  - War Department, Discharges, 1946-08-31 (Box 150)
  - Seneca Ordnance Depot, 1946-09-01 (Box 150)
  - War Department, General, 1946-09-01 (Box 150)
  - A, 1947-1948 (Box 83)
  - Extra Broadcasts, John Taber, 1947 (Box 155)
  - Extra Statements, John Taber, 1947 (Box 155)
  - Statements and Broadcasts, John Taber, 1947 (Box 155)
  - B-Z, 1948 (Box 83)
  - Newspapers, 38th District, 1949 (Box 159)
  - State Department, 1949 (Box 160)
  - Treasury Department, 1949 (Box 160)
  - War Assets Administration, 1949 (Box 160)
  - Agricultural Yearbook, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Agriculture, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Air Force, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Appointments, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Army, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Army - Civil, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Auburn Chamber of Commerce, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Capitol, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Cayuga County Republican Committee, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administration, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Civil Service Employment, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Civil Service Retirement, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Coast Guard, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Commerce Department, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Condolences, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Congressional Directory, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Congressional Record, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Cortland County Republican Committee, 1950 (Box 157)
  - Employment, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Farm Bulletins, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Federal Bids, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Federal Security Agency, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Fish and Wildlife, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Football tickets, 1950 (Box 158)
  - General Services Administration, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Housing, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Interior, 1950 (Box 158)
  - International Harvester, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Introductory Letters, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Invitations, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Invitations - Open, 1950 (Box 158)
  - James Camellia, 1950 (Box 158)
  - John Taber Rebuttal, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Justice Department, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Labor Department, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Letters of Recommendations, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Marine Corps, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Miscellaneous, Subject, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Navy, General, 1950 (Box 159)
  - New York Republican Delegation, 81st Congress, 1950 (Box 159)
  - New York State Matters, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Office of Temporary Control, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Ontario County Republican Committee, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Passports, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Post Office, General Correspondence, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Publications, 1950 (Box 159)
  - R.F.C., 1950 (Box 159)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Referrals, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Sampson Air Force Base, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Sampson Property, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Selective Service, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Seneca County Hospital, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Seneca County Republican Committee, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Seneca Ordnance Depot - Personnel, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Social Security, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Hanson for Congress Propaganda, 1950 (Box 158)
  - State Department, 1950 (Box 159)
  - To and From Virginia, Auburn, 1950 (Box 158)
  - Treasury Department, 1950 (Box 159)
  - War Claims Commission, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Wayne County Republican Committee, 1950 (Box 159)
  - Auburn, 1951 (Box 151)
  - Condolences, 1951 (Box 152)
  - Reapportionment, New York State, 1951 (Box 153)
  - Interior Department, 1952 (Box 153)
  - Agriculture, 1953 (Box 155)
  - Armed Services, 1953 (Box 155)
  - A - C, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Acknowledgements, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Agricultural District - pamphlet, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Agriculture Year Book, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Air Force, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Airport, Newark, N.Y., Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Army, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Army - Civil, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Army - Closed, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Atlanta National Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Atomic Energy, 83rd Congress, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Auburn Chamber of Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Auburn VA Office, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Banking and Currency, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Blanks - Bills and Resolutions, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Budget, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Capital, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Cayuga County, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Cayuga County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Census Bureau, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Central District - pamphlet, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Civil Aeronautical Board, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administrations, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Civil Service and Employment, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Civil Service and Retirement, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Civilian Conservation Corps, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Civilian Conservation Corps, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Civilian Defense, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Coal and Fuel, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Coast Guard, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Coast Guard, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Coast Guard 2, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Cold Storage Corporation, Marion, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Columbia Rope Company, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Commerce Department, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Commerce Department, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Communications Commission, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Congressional Directory, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Congressional Record, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Congressional Record, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Conscription, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Constitutional Commission, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Contributions and Donations, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Cortland County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 151)
  - Customs, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Dairymen's League, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - District of Columbia, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Dole, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Eastern District - pamphlet, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Economic Stabilization Agency, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Employees' Compensation Commission, Date Unknown (Box 149)
  - Employment, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Fair haven National Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Farm Bulletins, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Farm Bulletins, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Farm Bureau, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Farm Credit, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Federal Bids, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Federal Civil Defense Administration, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Federal Emergency Relief, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Federal Housing Administration, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Federal Housing Administration, Date Unknown (Box 149)
  - Federal Security Agency, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Federal Trade Commission, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Federal Works Agency, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Fish, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Fish and Wildlife, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Flood Control, Date Unknown (Box 47)
  - Football tickets, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Foreign Affairs and Aid, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Foreign Service, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Forestry, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - General Accounting Office, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - General Services Administration, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Government Printing Office, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Great Modus Bay, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Gulf Atlantic Canal, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Handbook - Veterans Assistance Program, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Hawaii and Alaska, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Home Owners' Loan, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Home Owners Loan Corporation, Date Unknown (Box 149)
  - Hoover Commission, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Housing, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Housing, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Housing Administration, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - I - M, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - I - Z, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Income Tax, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Interior Department, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Interior Department, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Interior Department, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Interlayer Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Internal Revenue, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - International Harvester, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - International Harvester, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Introductory Letters, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Introductory Letters, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Introductory Letters, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Invitations, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Invitations, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Invitations, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Judiciary, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Justice, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Justice Department, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Justice Department, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Korea, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Labor, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Labor Board, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Labor Department, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Labor Department, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Labor Relations Board, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Lawyers, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Legislation, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Library of Congress, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Library of Congress, Date Unknown (Box 149)
  - Lyons Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Lyons Bank, sub-title, Davit National Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Manpower Commission, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Marine Corps, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Marine Corps, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Marion National Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Maritime Commission, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Medicine, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Merchant Marines and Fisheries, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Metropolitan District - pamphlet, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Congressional, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Miscellaneous, Subject, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Munitions Board, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - N - S, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - N.Y.A., Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, Date Unknown (Box 49)
    Folder 1 includes Dewey, Goliath Osborne correspondence
  - N.Y.S. Matters, Date Unknown (Box 49)
    Folder 2 includes Thomas Dewey correspondence, 1943, and one letter from Martin P. Fatherhood, Sept. 13, 1943
  - Naples P.O., Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - National Defense, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - National Defense Council, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - National Federation of Independent Business - Ballots, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - National Production Authority, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - National Science Foundation, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Navy Commissions and Enlisted Ratings, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Navy Department, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Navy, General, Date Unknown (Box 49)
  - Navy, General, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - New York Republican Delegation, 82nd Delegation, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - New York State Matters, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Newark Banks, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Newspapers, 38th District, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - North Rose First National Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Office of Education, Date Unknown (Box 152)
  - Ontario County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Passports, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Patents, Date Unknown (Box 150)
  - Pensions, State and Federal; Social Security and Unemployment Insurance, Date Unknown (Box 150)
  - Phelps Bank or Phelps National Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Post Office, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Price Stabilization, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Public Lands, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Public Works, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Publications, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Publications, Date Unknown (Box 150)
  - Railroad Retirement, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Red Creek Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Referrals, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Rivers and Harbors Committee, Date Unknown (Box 48)
  - Romulus Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Route 20 - Auburn, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Rules Committee, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Salary Stabilization, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Sampson, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Sampson Property, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Savannah Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Schuyler County, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Selective Service, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Selective Service, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Seneca County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Stateless Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Social Security, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Modus Bank, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - St. Lawrence Project, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - State Department, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - State Department, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - To Take Trips in District, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Townsend Plan, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Treasury Department, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Unamerican Activities, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - United Nations, 83rd Congress, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Universal Military Training, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Veterans Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Washington - To and From, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Wayne County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Ways and Means Committee, Date Unknown (Box 155)
  - Yates County Republican Committee, Date Unknown (Box 153)
  - Veterans
    - McDonald, John R., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Myers, Rufus, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - V. A. O'Toole, Thomas, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Pollack, Charles, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Simms, Henry, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Fluty, George, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Low-born, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Wallace, C. Stewart, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Wires, Mrs., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Andrews, Stuart, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Basso, Robert Henry, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Champagne, John, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Christian, Vincent, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Devolves, Michael G., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Lard, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Hooker, Roger F., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Hyper, Elvin, Date Unknown (Box 37)